The Kingdom of Fiore...
It's a stable neutral country
with a population of 17 million.
It is a world filled with magic.
Magic is traded like common goods.
It has become a part of daily life.
And there are people
who use magic to make a living.
Those people are called "Mages".
Mages belong to various guilds
and perform their jobs on request.
Countless guilds have been formed
in this country.
And there's a certain mage guild
located in a city.
In past times... no, even now,
it's still creating legends...
Its name is...
...Fairy Tail.
Fairy, where are you going
I'll collect all the light
to make your future shine
Oh yeah,
can you hear my voice?
Oh yeah, I'm screaming it out
with my virile voice
Oh yeah, I'll scream
until my voice reaches your heart
Oh yeah, oh yeah
Like the moon
and sun's high touch
Didn't you forget anything?
I won't be able
to find what I desire
If your amusing presence
isn't by my side
Snowing, the times
we got close to each other
Brought forth
your honest smile
Fairy, where are you going
I'll collect all the light
to make your future shine
Don't say goodbye
The port city, Hargeon.
U-Um, mister?
Natsu!
We've arrived at Hargeon!
Get up! Get up!
I-Is he alright?
Yes!
This happens all the time.
It is hopeless.
I will never ride a train ever again...
If the information is correct,
Salamander should be in this town.
Let's go.
L-Let me rest
for a little bit...
Save me!!
It departed.
Fairy Tail
What?
This is the only magic store
in this town?
Yes. Because fishing is more prosperous
than magic in this town.
Only 10% of the citizens
can use magic.
This store
is mainly for traveling mages.
Ah~
I guess I came here for nothing.
Well, well, before saying that
take a look at this, please.
I have lots of new goods, too!
This Color Magic is probably
the most popular one among girls!
You can change your clothes' color
depending on your mood.
Just say "Change"!
I already have it.
Youhou!
I am looking
for powerful Gate Keys.